Willowbrook Review Panel; Records apap127
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files [RESTRICTED], 1972-1981; 9; 7.7 cubic ft.
  - National Association for Retarded Citizens [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - National Association of Social Workers [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - National Commission for the Protection of Human Subjects of Biomedical and Behavioral Research [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Nebraska Consent Decree [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Nebraska, Horacek v. Exon Consent Agreement [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Nebraska, Psychiatric Institute University of Nebraska [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - New York City, Board Of Education [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - New York City, Human Resources Administration Division of Post, Institutional Services [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - New York City, Department of Mental Health and Mental Retardation Services [RESTRICTED], 1975-1978 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - New York State, Audit and Control, Department of [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - New York State, Audit and Control, Department of [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - New York State, Audit and Control, Department of [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - New York State, Budget, Division of the [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - New York State, Civil Service, Department of the [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - New York State, Education, Department of [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - New York State, Mental Retardation, Division of [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - New York State, Protection and Advocacy System for Developmental Disabilities [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - New York State, Social Services, Department of [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Newsletters, Reports and Announcements Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - O'Berry Center [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - O'Neall, Linda/Florida Project [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - Pennsylvania Association for Retarded Citizens [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
  - Persons to Receive Recommendations and Reports [RESTRICTED], 1977; Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - Porter, Novelli, and Associates [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
  - President's Committee on Mental Retardation [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
  - Presidential Programming Checklist [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
  - Protection and Advocacy System for Developmental Disabilities Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
  - Protection and Advocacy System for Developmental Disabilities Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
  - Protection and Advocacy System for Developmental Disabilities Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 5 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Protection and Advocacy System for Developmental Disabilities Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 5 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Regional Council on Mental Retardation [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978 (Box 5 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Rothman, David, Center for Policy Research Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1976; 1978 (Box 5 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Rothman, David, Proposal for Deinstitutionalization Evaluation [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 5 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Service Delivery System Accreditation [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 5 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Directory of National Information Sources on Handicapping Conditions and Related Services [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 6 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - United States Department of Health Education and Welfare, Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1972; 1977 (Box 6 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Report of the Secretary's Special Federal Team: The New York State Mental Retardation Program, October 1972 [RESTRICTED] (Box 6 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - United States Public Health Service Hospital [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 6 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Advisory Boards Consumer Advisory Board, Appeal of Developmental Plan For Michael Gagen [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Advisory Bodies, Consumer Advisory Board, Resident [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Advisory Bodies, Consumer Advisory Board, Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Advisory Bodies, Professional Advisory Board [RESTRICTED], 1978; 1980 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Advisory Bodies, Professional Advisory Board, Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Agency Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Appendices 11-26 [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Appendices 11-26 [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Appendices 27-46 [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Appendices 27-46 [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Residents [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Autopsies and Death Investigations [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Aversive Conditioning [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Case Management [RESTRICTED], 1977; 1979-1980 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Case Management [RESTRICTED], 1977; 1979-1980 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Case Manager Caseload Summaries [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Case Management Issues [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Case Management Report, Draft [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Clothing Questionnaire [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Resident, Case History and Treatment Plan [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - F.B.I [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Family Care, Court Documents [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Family Care Program, Notice of Motion in U.S District Court [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Florida Association for Retarded Citizens et. al. v. Graham et. al., Complaint [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Georgia Retardation Center [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Resident [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - Resident, Death Case [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - Individual Clients [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
  - Institutes of Applied Human Dynamics [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - Institutional Returns [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
  - Kennedy, Rose F., Center for Research in Mental Retardation and Human Development [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
  - Resident, Quarterly Developmental Plan [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 7 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
  - Legal Aid Society of Minneapolis [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Legal Aid Society of Minneapolis [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Legislative Interest [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Resident [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Mental Health Information Services [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Mental Health Law Project [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Mental Health Law Project, Maine Consent Decree [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Mental Health Law Project, Maine Consent Decree (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Mental Retardation, General Information [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Michigan Association for Retarded Children [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - National Association for Retarded Citizens, Publications List [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU) [RESTRICTED], 1978-1980 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - New York State, Comptroller, Office of the [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - New York State, Developmental Plan Training Proposal [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - New York State, Health, Department of [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Non-Residential Clients of Willowbrook as of March 17 [RESTRICTED], 1972; 1977-1981 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Non-Residential Clients of Willowbrook as of March 17 [RESTRICTED], 1972; 1977-1981 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Non-Residential Clients of Willowbrook as of March 17 [RESTRICTED], 1972; 1977-1981 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Non-Residential Clients of Willowbrook as of March 17 [RESTRICTED], 1972; 1977-1981 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Resident [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Pennhurst State School and Hospital (Pennsylvania) [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Pennhurst State School and Hospital (Pennsylvania) [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Presidential Commission on Mental Health [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 8 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Post-Institutional Placement Program (PIPP) [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Post-Institutional Placement Program (PIPP) [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Post-Institutional Placement Program (PIPP) [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Rutgers Toilet Training Program [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Rutgers Toilet Training Program [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Psychotropic Drug Use, Problems [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Self Injuries Behavior, Sensory Awareness Training [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Resident [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Residence Pre-Opening Surveys [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Resident [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Resident [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Resident [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Resident [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Residents, Program Review [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Staffing, Training [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Staffing, Training [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - State Hiring Freeze, Procedures [RESTRICTED], 1978-1980 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Subpoena Forms [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - System Wide Reports [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Resident [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Wyatt v. Ireland (Partlow State School and Hospital Alabama) [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Wyatt v. Ireland (Partlow State School and Hospital, Alabama) [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Box 9 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Wyatt v. Ireland (Partlow State School and Hospital, Alabama) [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Box 10 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Wyatt v. Ireland (Partlow State School and Hospital, Alabama) [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Box 10 (9-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
- Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980; 10; 2.6 cubic ft.
  This series consists of 2.5 cubic feet of files related to complaints and inquiries received and investigated by the Willowbrook Review Panel. Many of these complaints came from parents or guardians of Willowbrook class members, expressing concern about conditions at facilities or in community placements. Other complaints came from facility employees, claiming that they had observed disregard for the mandates of the Consent Decree while on the job. There are also records of general inquiries about the Review Panel and the Consent Decree from students, the news media, and others.
  Most of the material is organized chronologically, with each month's folder containing a summary of complaints and inquiries as well as supporting documents, mostly correspondence. However, there are also a few files for individual facilities. There is extensive documentation of the case of Sharon Solnica, including many transcripts from Board of Education hearings. Sharon's parents sought to have her educated at the Institute for Applied Human Dynamics while in residence at the Bernard Fineson Developmental Center (BFDC). Fineson staff members argued that the hour-long bus ride from BFDC to the Institute was detrimental to Sharon's progress. Also included in this series are files related to a complaint made by a Willowbrook staff member, Pricilla Sarino, to the Review Panel. Sarino provided the Panel with several hundred pages of Willowbrook internal memoranda and other documents to support her complaint. The series is restricted because it contains information about specific named residents of Willowbrook and other state developmental centers.
  Arranged alphabetically and chronologically.
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1976 February (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1976 March (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1976 April (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1976 May (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1976 June (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1976 July (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1976 August (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1976 September (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1976 November (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1976 December (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1977 January (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1977 February (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1977 March (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1977 March (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1977 April (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1977 May (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1977 May (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1977 June (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1977 July (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1977 August (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1977 September (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1977 October (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1977 November (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1977 December (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1978 January (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1978 March (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1978 April (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1978 May (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1978 June (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1978 July (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1978 August (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1978 September (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1978 October (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1978 November (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1978 December (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1979 January (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1979 February (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 39)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1979 March (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 40)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1979 April (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 41)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1979 May (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 42)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1979 June (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 43)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1979 July (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 44)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1979 July (Box 1 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 45)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1979 July (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1979 September (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1979 September (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1979 September (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1979 October (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1979 November (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1979 December (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1980 January (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1980 February (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1980 March (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1980 April (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED], 1980 May (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Complaints and Inquiries, Bernard Fineson Development Center [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Complaints and Inquiries, Resident [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Complaints and Inquiries, Resident [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Complaints and Inquiries, Resident [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Complaints and Inquiries, Haven Facility [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Complaints and Inquiries, Long Island Facilities [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Complaints and Inquiries, Manhattan Facilities [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Complaints and Inquiries, Mental Retardation Institute [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Complaints and Inquiries, Resident Incident [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Complaints and Inquiries, Resident Incident [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Complaints and Inquiries, Resident [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Complaints and Inquiries, Resident Complaint [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 2 (10-Complaints and Inquiries [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)